Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- Miscellaneous, A-Z Materials, 1916-1931
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 75)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 76)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 77)
    Hutchison, C. B.
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 78)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 79)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 80)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 81)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 82)
    Shepardson, Whitney H.
  - J Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 83)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 84)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 85)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 86)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 87)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 88)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 89)
  - Legislative Index Publishing Company, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 90)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 91)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 92)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 93)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 94)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 95)
  - Mann, A. R., Expense Account, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 96)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 97)
  - Morrisville, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Morrisville, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Morrisville, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Morrisville, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - International Education Board - Mann, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - National Research Council, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - National Research Council, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - National Research Council, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - National Research Council, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Printing, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Robinson, James R., 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Supplies, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Witter, D. P., 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Wessels, P. H., 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - White, Horace, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - American Country Life Association, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Cobleskill, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Dairymen's League, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Extension Service News, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Farmingdale, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Fellowships, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Fellowships, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - G.L.F. Exchange, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - International Country Life Commission, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Morrisville, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Robinson, J. R., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Max Schling Loan Fund, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Supplies, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Supplies, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - White, Horace, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Wessels, P. H., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Witter, D. P., 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous, 1927-1928 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Animal Husbandry Conference, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Agricultural Society - College of Agriculture, Constitutions and By-Laws, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - American Country Life Association, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - American Country Life Association, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - American Country Life Association, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 59)
  - Cobleskill, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - Class Reunion - 1904, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - Class Reunion - 1904, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - Class Reunion - 1904, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - Class Reunion - 1904, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - Class Reunion - 1904, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - Dairymen's League, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 70)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 71)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 72)
  - Farmingdale, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 73)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 74)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 75)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 76)
  - G.L.F., 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 77)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 78)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 79)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 80)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 81)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 82)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 83)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 84)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 85)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 86)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 87)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 46, Folder 88)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Mann, A. R., Expense Account, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Mann, A. R., Expense Account, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Morrisville, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - National Research Council, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - National Research Council, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - National Research Council, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Projects - General Correspondence, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Projects - General Correspondence, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Supplies, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - White, Horace, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Wessels, P. H., 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Witter, P. H., 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Workmen's Compensation Blank, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - X,Y,Z Miscellaneous, 1928-1929 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - American Country Life Association, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    Landis, Benson Y.
  - American Country Life Association, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Cobleskill, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Cornelian Council, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Library Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Dairymen's League, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Farmingdale, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - Ginn and Company, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - G.L.F. Exchange, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Institute of International Education, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Mann, A. R., Expense Account, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Morrisville, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - National Research Council, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - National Research Council, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - North Eastern Experiment Stations, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - North Eastern Experiment Stations, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - North Eastern Experiment Stations, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - North Eastern Experiment Stations, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Supplies, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - White, Horace, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Wessels, P. H., 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Witter, D. P., 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Burritt, M. C., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - County Library Committee, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Cobleskill, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Dairymen's League, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Farmingdale, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Ginn and Company, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - G.L.F. Exchange, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Institute of International Education, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Mann, A. R., Expense Account, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Morrisville, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Reisner, J. H., 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Resolutions, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Supplies, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - White, Horace, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 46)